<!DOCTYPE idea-plugin PUBLIC "Plugin/DTD" "http://plugins.intellij.net/plugin.dtd">
<idea-plugin url="http://plugins.intellij.net/plugin/?id=3749">

    <name>${plugin.name}</name>
    <id>${plugin.id}</id>
    <version>${project.version}</version>

    <description>
        Launches VisualVM's Java profiler from within IDEA. VisualVM is based on NetBeans Profiler and is bundled
        with JDK 6 Update 7 and above. VisualVM may also be downloaded for free from https://visualvm.dev.java.net/
    </description>
    <category>Profiling</category>

    <vendor url="http://www.orfjackal.net" logo="/net/orfjackal/visualvm4idea/icons/logo-16.png">Esko Luontola</vendor>

    <idea-version since-build="9000" until-build="9999"/>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
        <p>0.4.2 (2008-11-26)
        <br>- Fixed possible NPE if the MainClass returned by IDEA was null
        </p>

        <p>0.4.1 (2008-11-24)
        <br>- Fixed inconsistent naming of profiler actions (IDEA 8 only)
        <br>- Fixed the profiler actions appearing in every file's context menu (IDEA 8 only)
        </p>

        <p>0.4.0 (2008-11-24)
        <br>- Compatible with IDEA 8
        <br>- Uniquely identify the application launched by IDEA
        </p>

        <p>0.3.0 (2008-11-12)
        <br>- Memory profiling
        <br>- Settings are copied to VisualVM's user interface
        <br>- Saved space in the run configuration dialog by moving help texts to tooltips
        </p>

        <p>0.2.0 (2008-11-09)
        <br>- Works with the bundled VisualVM which comes with JDK 6 Update 7 and above
        <br>- Detects bundled VisualVMs automatically, in which case no configuration is necessary
        <br>- Should work also with Linux and Mac (not tested, also not sure about 64 bit JVMs)
        <br>- Defaults to jdk15 profiler interface for better compatibility (hardcoded)
        <br>- Warns about invalid configuration
        </p>

        <p>0.1.0 (2008-11-06)
        <br>- Initial release
        <br>- CPU profiling (Windows Java 6 only)
        </p>

        <p>Known issues
        <br>- VisualVM may freeze if the application finishes execution before its window opens up in VisualVM
        </p>

        <p>Future plans
        <br>- A button for opening the currently running (non-profiled) program in VisualVM
        <br>- Integration with NetBeans IDE's profiler if it has benefits over VisualVM (they both use internally the same NetBeans Profiler)
        </p>
    ]]></change-notes>

    <application-components>
        <component>
            <implementation-class>net.orfjackal.visualvm4idea.plugin.PluginSettingsComponent</implementation-class>
        </component>
    </application-components>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <executor implementation="net.orfjackal.visualvm4idea.plugin.CpuProfilerExecutor"/>
        <executor implementation="net.orfjackal.visualvm4idea.plugin.MemoryProfilerExecutor"/>
        <programRunner implementation="net.orfjackal.visualvm4idea.plugin.CpuProfilerRunner"/>
        <programRunner implementation="net.orfjackal.visualvm4idea.plugin.MemoryProfilerRunner"/>
    </extensions>

</idea-plugin>
